Guide to the Walter Freeman, Class of 1916, Yale College, Photograph Albums Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Volume V (?)
  - Page 6
    - 1610. Chapel exit (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1611. (Gateway between Bingham and Welch) (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1612. College Street (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1613. Center Church (through Phelps Gate) (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Page 7
    - 1614. The Bowl, May 1914 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1615. H.A. Farr (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1616. Ticket distribution (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1617. Before Sunday chapel (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1618. Gun practice (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1619. Yale Bowl, 1914 November (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1620. News Heeler (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Page 8
    - 1621. Bill Eckman and Soc Innes (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1622. Men of Yale (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1623. Painting at Henley (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1624. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1625. R.A. Gardner, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - 1626. Beachey, May 1912 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Page 9
    - 1627. H.M. Johnstone at Intercollegiates, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1628. Soccer, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1629. Penn relays, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1630. (Track), 1912 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1631. F.M. Hapeth, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1632. W.M. Oler at 6 ft., 1916 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1633. Schiller (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1634. Walker Exeter Interscholastics (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1635. Intercollegiates (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1636. Gulliver (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1637-38. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Page 10
    - 1639. Southern California Rush (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1640. Wagoner, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1641. Wagoner/Gardner/Pat (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1642. Blossom (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1643. [Track] (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1644. Football at target practice (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1645. Southern California (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1646-47. [Soccer] (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - 1648. Hockey squad starts to run (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Page 11
    - 1649. In the baseball cage (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1650. Entrance to swimming pool (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1651. Old hockey rink (torn down 1914) (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1652. Sweeney (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1653. New rink; first ice, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Page 12
    - 1654. Wrestling Yale-Penn (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1655. Ready for a run (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1656. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1657. Squad, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - 1658. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Page 13
    - 1659. On the machines (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - 1660. [Crew], 1913 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - 1661-62. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Page 14
    - 1663. [Boathouse] (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - 1664. Fall, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - 1665. [Boathouse, bringing out sculls] (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - 1666. Locking oars (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Page 15
    - 1667. Yale-Penn meet, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - 1668. Cross-country squad (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - 1669. Treadway, 1917, Walker, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - 1670. WW Childs, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Page 16
    - 1671. 220 Teschner beats Cornell, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - 1672. Donnelly announcer, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - 1673. Diggs, 1913 Law (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - 1674. 100 Teschner, Cornell, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - 1675. 220 finish (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Page 17
    - 1676. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1677. Gym leaders (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1678. Hockey at rink (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1679. Parade to Brown game, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1680. 220 dash, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1681. Treadway, fall meet, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1682. Class relay, fall 1918 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1683. Waters vs. Avery, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1684. (?) vs. Princetonian, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Page 18
    - 1685. Jumping in the Cage (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1686. Rehearsing the fight for spring play, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1687. Rhinoceros race vs. Northfield, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1688. World record mile (Caldwell beats Brown) (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1689. MS Chism (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1690. Stickwork on Lake Whitney (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1691-93. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Page 19
    - 1694. Wagoner (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1695. Queal, Booth (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1696. First cross-country run, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1697. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1698. Barrell (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1699. Yale-Harvard X-country race (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1700. Blocking a try (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Page 20
    - 1701. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1702. X-country squad (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1703. Haverford soccer (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1704. X-country squad (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1705. Loughridge (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1706. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1707. Early track work (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1708. DG Acheson, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Page 21
    - 1709. Yale-Penn, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1710. 100 yard dash (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1711. Cook (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1712. 1913 track team (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1713. MR Diggs, 1913 L.S. (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1714. Northfield sports (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Page 22
    - 1715. Spring meet, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1716. Johnstone (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1717. 1916 freshmen track, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1718. Wagoner (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1719. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1720. 1913 spring meet (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Page 23
    - 1721. Yale-Brown parade, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1722. Taft parade (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1723. Easter exodus, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1724. Cheering the crew off (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1725. Taft parade (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1726. Corporation meeting; Taft appointed (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1727. [Parade] (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1728. [Parade] (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Page 24
    - 1729. Taft-- auto in station (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1730. Taft in balcony (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1731. The address by Taft (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - 1732. Start of southern trip, baseball team (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Page 25
    - 1733. Brown [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1734. [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1735. Blossom [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1736. Early practice [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1737. L.S. Middlebrook [baseball], 1915 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1738. HA Pumpelly [baseball], 1915 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1739-40. [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Page 26
    - 1741. [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1742. Legor [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1743-45. [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1746. Yale-Penn, Burdette (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1747. [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1748. Yale-Princeton, baseball, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1749. Blossom, [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1750-51. [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1752. A. Lane, 1916 [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1753. Walsh [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - 1754-56. [baseball] (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Page 27
    - 1757-58. Peabody Collection (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - 1759. Crew quarters (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - 1760. Peabody Collection (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - 1761. Battell Chapel (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - 1762. Sophomore fence (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Page 28
    - 1763. Memorial Hall (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - 1764. Vanderbilt archway (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - 1765. Memorial Hall (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - 1766. Library (Dwight) by moonlight (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Page 29
    - 1767. Brown game, Whiffenpoofs, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - 1768. Penn bowl guards (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - 1769. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - 1770. Gamble [soccer] (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - 1771. [Football, Whiffenpoofs] (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - 1772. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Page 30
    - 1773. Haber, B. [football] (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - 1774. Harvard, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - 1775-76. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Page 31
    - 1777. [high jump] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1778. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1779. [track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1780. [Pottey, Shedden, hurdles] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1781. [Brown, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1782. [Frost, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1783. [Oler, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1784. Intercollegiate x-country, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Page 32
    - 1785. Lyman/N. Platt [track], 1916 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1786. [Brown, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1787. In the old bowling alleys, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1788. [Overton, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1789. ½ mile run, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1790. [Acheson, Snowden, Gold] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1791. JP Jones wins mile, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1792. [Revell/MacDonald, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1793. [Revell, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1794. [Platt, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1795. [Lyman, 1913, track] (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - 1796. [Flash, baseball] (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Page 33
    - 1797. Lefty Blynn, 1912 (football) (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1798. Touchdown by Colgate, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1799-1801. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1802. Between the halves (football), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1803-05. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1806. Princeton (Wilson) [football], 1913 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1807-10. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Page 34
    - 1811. Guernsey punts (Princeton), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1812-14. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1815. Princeton (football), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1816. Harvard-Princeton football, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - 1817. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Page 35
    - 1818. Wright hall, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1819. Gaton Locks, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1820. Grub St. (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1821. From Dwight (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1822. Chapel after snow (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Page 36
    - 1823. Wright Court (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1824. Chapel exit (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1825. Elm St. (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1826. Diabolo Cooney, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1827. York Street fire, 1914 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - 1828-29. Wright Hall (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Page 37
    - 1830. Bomeisler, Carlin (football) (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1831. Bull, Jones (football) (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1832. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1833. Freshman football game (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1834. WT Bull, 1888S (football) (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1835. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Page 38
    - 1836. Philbin, 1913 (football) (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1837. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1838. Yale 0/Maine 0 (football), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1839-40. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1841. Legore (football) (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - 1842. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Page 39
    - 1843. Riddell 1913S (baseball) (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1844. Providence (baseball) (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1845. Yale-Brown (baseball) (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1846. Capt. and coach (baseball), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1847. 2 bagger by Blossom (baseball) (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1848. Hanoy, 1915S (baseball) (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1849. Yale-Princeton (baseball), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1850. Riddell safe, Yale-Princeton, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1851-52. [Baseball] (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1853. P.B.K.--faculty--Mendel puts out A.B. Crawford (baseball), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1854-55. [Baseball] (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1856. Tufts (baseball) (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1857. [Baseball] (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Page 40
    - 1858. Capt. Merritt (baseball), 1912 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1859. [Baseball], 1913 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1860. Blossom and Quinsky (baseball), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1861. Yale-Brown (baseball), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1862-65. [Baseball] (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 1866. Yale 2nd--Harvard 2nd/Osborn out (baseball) (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Page 41
    - 1867. Shedden, Houpt, Roseur (hurdles) (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1868. Wrestling match, 1917-18 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1869. Maxim, front lever, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1870. [Hurdles] (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1871. [Hockey] (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1872. [Track] (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Page 42
    - 1873. Tug-of-war/ southern California, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1874. Maxim (gymnastics) (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1875. Crew, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1876. Potter, 1914S, Shedden, 1915 (hurdles) (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1877. Soccer (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1878. [Water polo] (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - 1879-80. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Page 43
    - 1881. Amherst (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1882. CCNY (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1883. Burlington, VT 1914 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1884. CCNY (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1885. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1886. Columbia University (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Page 44
    - 1887. New boathouse, Gales Ferry, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1888. Cairo, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1889. Prize photo (CT Hall, Vanderbilt), 1915 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1890-91. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - 1892. Old Campus facing Durfee (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Page 45
    - 1893-94. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - 1895. Penn fresh (Randall, president), 1916 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - 1896-98. [football] (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Page 46
    - 1899. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - 1900. Lateral pass to Guernsey (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - 1901. Tucker (football) (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - 1902. Knowles (football), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - 1903-04. [Football] (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Page 47
    - 1905. Power plant (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1906. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1907. Gov. Simeon Baldwin (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1908. In the Bowl (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1909. 1913 News board (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Page 48
    - 1910. Oxford (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1911-12. Hockey rink (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1913. Jones and Merritt (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1914. Bones-- new building (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - 1915. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Page 49
    - 1916. Brown (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1917. Vermont baseball, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1918. [Polo], 1912 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1919. Bomeisher (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1920. [Baseball], 1914 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1921. Cormish, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1922. [Baseball], 1914 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1923. Brown hits, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1924-25. Baseball players (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1926. Reilly, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Page 50
    - 1927. World Series, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1928. Rounding third (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1929. Pumpelly safe, Brown game, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1930. Reilly bunts (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1931. 7th inning (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1932. Early spring baseball practice (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1933. Middlebrook (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1934. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1935. [Baseball, bench] (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - 1936. Vaughn, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Page 51
    - 1937. Crew, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1938. Dunn (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1939. Basketball (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1940. Baseball players (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1941. Fencing (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1942. Rees (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1943. Handball (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Page 52
    - 1944. Wrestling (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1945. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1946. Soccer (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1947. Swim team, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1948. Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1949. Willets (bowling) (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1950. Macheish (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 1951. [Tennis] (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Page 53
    - 1952. [Pole vault] (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1953. J.P. Jones, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1954. Lyman, 1913, Booth (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1955. 1912-13 Basketball (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1956. Childs, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1957. Hurdles (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1958-59. Track (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Page 54
    - 1960. Intercollegiates, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1961. Pole vault (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1962. X-country (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1963. Track (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1964. Pole vault (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1965. X-country working out in gym (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1966. Oler (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1967. Swiliart (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - 1968. Pole vault (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Page 55
    - 1969-70. Baseball (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1971. Vaughn, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1972. Yale vs Amherst (baseball) (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1973. Scott (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Page 56
    - 1974. Osborn (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1975. Temmers (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1976. Middlebrook (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1977. Greys (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1978. [Baseball] (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1979. Quinby (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - 1980-81. [Baseball] (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Page 57
    - 1982. Sheff campus, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1983. Yale U. Press and Alumni Weekly building, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1984. Graduate School (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1985. Osborn Corner (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1986. Library [Dwight Hall] (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Page 58
    - 1987. Marquand Chapel (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1988. Porter Gateway (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1989. Chittenden (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1990. Porter Gateway (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1991. Unidentified building (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1992. Taft, 1914, March 28 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1993. Yale Bowl under construction (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - 1994. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Page 59
    - 1995. [Crew] (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 1996. Snowden, Rogers (coach) (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 1997. 1st crew Fresh, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 1998-2001. [Crew] (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2002. Harriman's yacht (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2003. [Crew] (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Page 60
    - 2004. [Crew--Barnum, Cox] (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2005. [Crew] (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2006. [Crew--McLane, Cox] (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2007. [Crew] (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2008. Mixed crew (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2009. [Crew] (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - 2010. 1st Dunham varsity, 1912 fall (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Page 61
    - 2011. Gateway next Osborn (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2012. 1916 fence (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2013. [Dwight Hall from Phelps Gate] (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2014. 1914 men (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2015. Alumni Day 1914 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Page 62
    - 2016. Boxer in Modern Gallery of the Art School (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2017. Commons at rest (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2018. Judge's Cave (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2019. Anxious parent (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2020. Shelden MacLeish (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - 2021. Dr. Anderson (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Page 63
    - 2022. Atho (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2023. Johnny Mack Queal (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2024. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2025. Stokes family (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2026. McKenzie (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2027. [Pole vault] (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Page 64
    - 2028. 1913 Fall meet (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2029. [Hurdles] (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2030. Diggs (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2031. [Shot put] (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2032. [Long jump] (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2033. Hammer throwers at the field (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2034. Booth, Quesl, Pat (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2035. Wilkie (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - 2036. Poucher, Scotter (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Page 65
    - 2037. Leland Stanford (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - 2038. 1914 (Yale fence) (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - 2039. 1913 (snowball fight) (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - 2040. Illinois marching band (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Page 66
    - 2041-45. 1913 (Whiffenpoof antics) (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Page 67
    - 2046. Johnstone, Penn Relays (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2047. Poncher (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2048. Biddle, P.E.A. (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2049. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2050. Offput (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2051. [Soccer] (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2052. Beatty (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2053. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2054. Roos (shot put) (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Page 68
    - 2055. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2056. Wagoner (pole vault) (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2057-59. 1913 (Track) (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2060. 1913 Fall meet (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2061. Roos, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - 2062. Cowles, Rickells, Blackmer, Cornell (runners) (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Page 69
    - 2063. Harper (diving) (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2064. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2065. Shedden (hurdles) (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2066. Talbot, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2067. Davidson (track), 1913 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2068. [Track], 1914 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2069. Record relay team (main runners), 1912-13 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2070. Queal (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Page 70
    - 2071. Harvard football, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2072. [Runners] (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2073. Princeton football, fatal forward pass over goal line, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2074. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2075. [Parade] (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2076. [Football] (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - 2077. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Page 71
    - 2078. [Runners] (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2079. [Long jump] (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2080. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2081. Fall meet (Revell, Blackmer, Cowles), 1912 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2082. Reidpath starts from scratch (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2083. [Track team preparing] (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2084. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2085. Whitney (shot put), 1914 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2086. Treadway (track), 1914 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Page 72
    - 2087. Samuels (gymnastics), 1913 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2088. [Fencing] (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2089. Platt Adams-Olympics (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2090. [Soccer] (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2091. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2092. Harvard, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2093. Gardiner, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - 2094. Yale-Harvard, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Page 73
    - 2095. Fresh hockey, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2096. Everand (gymnastics), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2097. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2098. Cook (long jump) (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2099. Hanstwick (high jump) (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2100. Anderson, Foster (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2101. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2102. [Soccer] (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2103. King (boxing) (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Page 74
    - 2104. Blackmer, Cowles, Cornell (track) (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2105. Cornell (track) (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2106. Douglas (track) (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2107. Knapp, Smith (track) (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2108. Roos (shot put) (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2109. [High jump] (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2110. [Pole vault] (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2111. [Revell] (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2112. Intercollegiates track meet, 1914; 440, Meredith (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2113. [Soccer] (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - 2114. [Hurdles] (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Page 75
    - 2115. [Baseball players] (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2116. Camp (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2117. Pompelly, Reilly, Hunter, Blossom, Cornish, Gile (Box 5, Folder 165)